{
    "id": "06a8c88eb9604e2a8eebea0118caf5f5",
    "title": "Concession and contrast: grammar worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9010325b3f144463987e8b22df457618",
            "title": "Concession And Contrast",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "....................................... working hard, he couldn’t pass the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In spite of",
                        "Although",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... it was late, we decided to go out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................. being rich, she is not happy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "Although",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................. having a bad teacher, she passed her test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In spite of",
                        "Although",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... she lives next door, we rarely see each other.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "However",
                        "Although",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................... facing many setbacks, he didn’t lose hope.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ being a foreigner, she speaks English remarkably well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In spite of",
                        "However",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................. she earns a good salary, she finds it difficult to make both ends meet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................................. living close to her office, she is always late for work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "However",
                        "Though",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................ working three jobs in a day, she makes it a point to spend quality time with her kids.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}